# Javad Rajabzade



ja7ad@live.com



linkedin.com/in/ja7ad



+989357738933



https://javad.id.ir

# Summary

I have over 7 years of experience in software development. A wide range of IT disciplines expert, with a focus on System Analysis, Design, Development, and Implementation of various applications, as well as experience with Clean Architecture, Master-Slave Architecture, and Infrastructure.

# **Experience**



# 🦠 Software Engineer

Ramooz

Jan 2022 - Present (1 month +)



### Back End Developer

معماران داده | Memaran Dadeh

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 (4 months)

Implement instamarkt.nl shop promotion and optimization

# Senior Software Engineer

#### farageek

Apr 2021 - Nov 2021 (8 months)

Blockchain knowledge of the Filecoin network and implementation of Filecoin Lotus optimization and R&D

- Implement Lotus Devnet
- Optimization
- Provide solutions to infrastructure issues
- Implement smart miner tool work with nanopool



# Senior Product Manager

#### Moeinsoft

Nov 2017 - Apr 2021 (3 years 6 months)

Moein Accounting Software, Anti-Ransomware Moein, MoeinBackup Development, Experience with InstallAware, Linux Administration

### Education



# **Islamic Azad University**

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering

2018 - 2020

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- **Exploring The Go (golang) Programming Language** Udemy UC-f0b7ae07-ac51-4bce-b7b7-3e589d0a72ba
- **Kubernetes by Doing: Kubernetes the Hard Way (CKA)** Udemy UC-0b4c8919-d113-48f1-9cea-58b1f20ba917
- Adobe XD: UI & UX Design with 14 real world project 2020 Udemy UC-b776555f-7de8-49a3-bf9f-285fe9cd739f
- Cyber Security and Ethical Hacking introduction Udemy UC-40890c72-3f09-4db0-86f7-f4793b5bd36d
- MYSQL Master Udemy
  UC-cfba71fa-2868-4dad-817e-63c207cfaa0f
- Backend Development in 2021 with Python, Django, SQLite3, Heroku, GIT Udemy
  UC-bdb3a893-2b94-4bd8-ac00-2e3d579b26db

#### **Skills**

Go (Programming Language) • Concurrent Programming • Linux System Administration • Python (Programming Language) • Blockchain • MySQL • Docker Products • Research and Development (R&D) • Microservices • MongoDB